(Howard:)I'm thinking about growing a goatee.
(Raj:)Actually that's a Van Dyke.
A goatee is just hair on the chin.
Oh. Wait, than what is it
if you just have hair up here?
You mean a mustache?
-Moo-stache!
-(SHOUTS) He said it!
(Raj:)Ha-ha, very funny.
Make fun of the foreign guy.
(Raj:)For your information,
there are four times as many Indians
(Raj:)as there are Americans,
so the way we say it is right.
(Howard:)-Say what?
-Moo-stache.
-(SHOUTS) Moo-stache!
-He said "moo-stache".
(Bernadette:)Guys, you're being childish.
(Sheldon:)She's right. You're grown men,
the kind who are perfectly capable
(Sheldon:)of growing your own moo-staches.
(Amy:)Hey, you were funny
on purpose, good job.
(Penny:)Hi. Sorry I'm late.
I was at an audition.
(Leonard:)-I'm sorry.
-You'll get 'em next time.
(Penny:)How about instead of assuming I
failed, you ask me how it went?
(Leonard:)Sorry. How did it go?
(Penny:)Just shut up.
(Raj:)Here, you can have your seat.
(Penny:)No, no, stay there.
I'm fine on the floor.
(Bernadette:)Have you guys ever thought about
getting a dining room table?
(Amy:)Yeah. You actually do have
room for one up there.